<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>Krebs on Security</title>
	<atom:link href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
	<link>http://krebsonsecurity.com</link>
	<description>In-depth security news and investigation</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 20:12:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.0.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Treasury Dept: Tor a Big Source of Bank Fraud</title>
		<link>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/treasury-dept-tor-a-big-source-of-bank-fraud/</link>
		<comments>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/treasury-dept-tor-a-big-source-of-bank-fraud/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 19:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BrianKrebs]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[A Little Sunshine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Fraud 2.0]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bank Secrecy Act]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Berkeley]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FinCEN]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Computer Science Institute]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nicholas Weaver]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Roger Dingledine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Suspicious Activity Reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[U.S. Treasury Department]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[University of California]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=28951</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A new report from the U.S. Treasury Department found that a majority of bank account takeovers by cyberthieves over the past decade might have been thwarted had affected institutions known to look for and block transactions coming through Tor, a global communications network that helps users maintain anonymity by obfuscating their true location online.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new report from the <strong>U.S. Treasury Department</strong> found that a majority of bank account takeovers by cyberthieves over the past decade might have been thwarted had affected institutions known to look for and block transactions coming through <a title="https://www.torproject.org/" href="https://www.torproject.org/" target="_blank">Tor</a>, a global communications network that helps users maintain anonymity by obfuscating their true location online.</p>
<p>The findings come in a non-public report obtained by KrebsOnSecurity that was produced by the <a title="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_Crimes_Enforcement_Network" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_Crimes_Enforcement_Network" target="_blank">Financial Crimes Enforcement Network</a> (FinCEN), a Treasury Department bureau responsible for collecting and analyzing data about financial transactions to combat domestic and international money laundering, terrorist financing and other financial crimes.</p>
<p>In the report, released on Dec. 2, 2014, FinCEN said it examined some 6,048 suspicious activity reports (SARs) filed by banks between August 2001 and July 2014, searching the reports for those involving one of more than 6,000 known Tor network nodes. Investigators found 975 hits corresponding to reports totaling nearly $24 million in likely fraudulent activity.</p>
<p>&#8220;Analysis of these documents found that few filers were aware of the connection to Tor, that the bulk of these filings were related to cybercrime, and that Tor related filings were rapidly rising,&#8221; the report concluded. &#8220;Our BSA [<a title="http://www.fincen.gov/statutes_regs/bsa/" href="http://www.fincen.gov/statutes_regs/bsa/" target="_blank">Bank Secrecy Act</a>] analysis of 6,048 IP addresses associated with the Tor <a title="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Darknet_(file_sharing)" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Darknet_(file_sharing)" target="_blank">darknet</a> [link added] found that in the majority of the SAR filings, the underlying suspicious activity &#8212; most frequently account takeovers &#8212; might have been prevented if the filing institution had been aware that their network was being accessed via Tor IP addresses.&#8221;</p>
<div id="attachment_28952" style="width: 610px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/fincen-bsa.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-28952" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/fincen-bsa-600x541.png" alt="Tables from the FinCEN report." width="600" height="541" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Tables from the FinCEN report.</p></div>
<p>FinCEN said it was clear from the SAR filings that most financial institutions were unaware that the IP address where the suspected fraudulent activity occurred was in fact a Tor node.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our analysis of the type of suspicious activity indicates that a majority of the SARs were filed for account takeover or identity theft,&#8221; the report noted. &#8220;In addition, analysis of the SARs filed with the designation &#8216;Other revealed that most were filed for &#8216;Account Takeover,&#8217; and at least five additional SARs were filed incorrectly and should have been &#8216;Account Takeover.'&#8221;</p>
<p>The government also notes that there has been a fairly recent and rapid rise in the number of SAR filings over the last year involving bank fraud tied to Tor nodes.</p>
<p>&#8220;From October 2007 to March 2013, filings increased by 50 percent,&#8221; the report observed. &#8220;During the most recent period &#8212; March 1, 2013 to July 11, 2014 &#8212; filings rose 100 percent.&#8221;<span id="more-28951"></span></p>
<p>While banks may be able to detect and block more fraudulent transactions by paying closer attention to or outright barring traffic from Tor nodes, such an approach is unlikely to have a lasting impact on fraud, said <strong>Nicholas Weaver</strong>, a researcher at the <strong>International Computer Science Institute</strong> (ICSI) and at the <strong>University of California, Berkeley</strong>.</p>
<p>&#8220;I’m not surprised by this: Tor is easy for bad actors to use to isolate their identity,&#8221; Weaver said &#8220;Yet blocking all Tor will do little good, because there are many other easy ways for attackers to hide their source address.&#8221;</p>
<p>Earlier this summer, the folks who maintain the Tor Project identified this problem &#8212; that many sites and even ISPs are increasingly blocking Tor traffic because of its abuse by fraudsters &#8212; as an existential threat to the anonymity network. The organization used this trend as<a title="https://blog.torproject.org/blog/call-arms-helping-internet-services-accept-anonymous-users" href="https://blog.torproject.org/blog/call-arms-helping-internet-services-accept-anonymous-users" target="_blank"> a rallying cry</a> for Tor users to consider lending their brainpower to help the network thrive in spite of these threats.</p>
<p>&#8220;<span class="pullquote pqright">A growing number of websites treat users from anonymity services differently Slashdot doesn&#8217;t let you post comments over Tor, Wikipedia won&#8217;t let you edit over Tor</span>, and Google sometimes gives you a captcha when you try to search (depending on what other activity they&#8217;ve seen from that exit relay lately),&#8221; wrote Tor Project Leader <strong>Roger Dingledine</strong>. &#8220;Some sites like Yelp go further and refuse to even serve pages to Tor users.&#8221;</p>
<p>Dingledine continued:</p>
<p>&#8220;The result is that the Internet as we know it is siloing. Each website operator works by itself to figure out how to handle anonymous users, and generally neither side is happy with the solution. The problem isn&#8217;t limited to just Tor users, since these websites face basically the same issue with users from open proxies, users from AOL, users from Africa, etc.</p>
<p>Weaver said the problem of high volumes of fraudulent activity coming through the Tor Network presents something of a no-win situation for any website dealing with Tor users.</p>
<p>&#8220;If you treat Tor as hostile, you cause collateral damage to real users, while the scum use many easy workarounds.  If you treat Tor as benign, the scum come flowing through,&#8221; Weaver said. &#8220;For some sites, such as Wikipedia, there is perhaps a middle ground. But for banks? That&#8217;s another story.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/treasury-dept-tor-a-big-source-of-bank-fraud/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>12</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bebe Stores Confirms Credit Card Breach</title>
		<link>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/bebe-stores-confirms-credit-card-breach/</link>
		<comments>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/bebe-stores-confirms-credit-card-breach/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 14:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BrianKrebs]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Data Breaches]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bebe stores breach]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bebe Stores credit card breach]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=28945</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In a statement released this morning, women's clothier chain bebe stores inc. confirmed news first reported on this blog Thursday: That hackers had stolen customer card data from stores across the country in a breach that persisted for several weeks last month.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a statement released this morning, women&#8217;s clothier chain <strong>bebe stores inc.</strong> confirmed news first reported on this blog Thursday: That hackers had stolen customer card data from stores across the country in a breach that persisted for several weeks last month.</p>
<div id="attachment_28933" style="width: 295px" class="wp-caption alignright"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/bebewiki.png"><img class="size-medium wp-image-28933" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/bebewiki-285x212.png" alt="Image: Wikipedia." width="285" height="212" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Image: Wikipedia.</p></div>
<p>Bebe stores said its investigation indicates that the breach impacted payment cards swiped in its U.S., Puerto Rico and U.S. Virgin Islands stores between Nov. 8, 2014 and Nov. 26, 2014. The data may have included cardholder name, account number, expiration date, and verification code.</p>
<p>The company emphasized that purchases made though its web site, mobile site/application, or in Canada or other international stores were not affected, and that customers should feel confident in continuing to use their payment cards in bebe stores.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our relationship with our customers is of the highest importance,&#8221; said bebe CEO <strong>Jim Wiggett</strong>, in a statement. &#8220;We moved quickly to block this attack and have taken steps to further enhance our security measures.&#8221;</p>
<p>Predictably, bebe stores is offering free credit monitoring services for one year to customers impacted by this incident, even though credit monitoring services do nothing to help consumers block fraud on existing accounts &#8212; such as credit and debit card accounts that may have been stolen in this breach.<br />
Consumers still need to keep a close eye on monthly statements, and report any unauthorized charges as quickly as possible.<span id="more-28945"></span></p>
<p>On Thursday, KrebsOnSecurity <a title="http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/banks-credit-card-breach-at-bebe-stores/" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/banks-credit-card-breach-at-bebe-stores/" target="_blank">reported</a> that several banks had complained about a pattern of fraudulent charges on customer credit cards that all had one thing in common: They&#8217;d all been used at bebe locations across the country. One bank contacted by this reporter also found several of its cards for sale in a brand new batch of stolen cards pushed onto the market in an underground &#8220;carding&#8221; shop, cards that all turned out to have been used at bebe stores during a two week period in the latter half of November.</p>
<p>Interestingly, when I first accessed <a title="http://www.bebe.com/content.jsp?pageName=protectingcustomers" href="http://www.bebe.com/content.jsp?pageName=protectingcustomers" target="_blank">the breach notification page</a> at bebe stores this morning, Kaspersky Antivirus flagged the page as a possible phishing attack (see screenshot below). This is most likely a false positive, but I thought it was worth mentioning anyway.</p>
<div id="attachment_28946" style="width: 610px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/bebe-kav.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-28946" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/bebe-kav-600x546.png" alt="Kaspersky Antivirus popped up this phishing page warning when I first tried to access the bebe stores breach alert." width="600" height="546" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Kaspersky Antivirus popped up this phishing page warning when I first tried to access the bebe stores breach alert.</p></div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/bebe-stores-confirms-credit-card-breach/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>10</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Banks: Credit Card Breach at Bebe Stores</title>
		<link>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/banks-credit-card-breach-at-bebe-stores/</link>
		<comments>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/banks-credit-card-breach-at-bebe-stores/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 15:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BrianKrebs]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Data Breaches]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bebe Stores credit card breach]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bebe Stores Inc breach]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[goodshop]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=28924</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Data gathered from several financial institutions and at least one underground cybercrime shop suggest that thieves have stolen credit and debit card data from Bebe Stores Inc., a nationwide chain of some 200 women&#8217;s clothing stores. Earlier this week, KrebsOnSecurity began hearing from different banks about a pattern of fraudulent charges on customer credit cards [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Data gathered from several financial institutions and at least one underground cybercrime shop suggest that thieves have stolen credit and debit card data from <strong>Bebe Stores Inc.</strong>, a nationwide chain of some 200 women&#8217;s clothing stores.</p>
<div id="attachment_28933" style="width: 295px" class="wp-caption alignright"><a class="lightbox" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/bebewiki.png"><img src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/bebewiki-285x212.png" alt="Image: Wikipedia." width="285" height="212" class="size-medium wp-image-28933" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Image: Wikipedia.</p></div>
<p>Earlier this week, KrebsOnSecurity began hearing from different banks about a pattern of fraudulent charges on customer credit cards that all had one thing in common: the cards were recently used at Bebe (pronounced &#8220;bee bee&#8221;) locations across the country.</p>
<p>This author reached out to Bebe via email and phone early Wednesday. Officials from Bebe Stores have not yet responded to requests for comment.</p>
<p>On Wednesday, this author heard from an East Coast bank which had purchased several of its customers cards that were being sold on a relatively new cybercrime shop called (<strong>goodshop[dot]bz]</strong>). The bank acquired cards from a batch that Goodshop released on Dec. 1, called &#8220;Happy Winter Update.&#8221; The prices from that Happy Winter batch range from $10 to $27 per card.</p>
<p>The bank found that all of the cards had been used at Bebe Stores in the United States between Nov. 18 and Nov. 28. It is not clear if the breach at Bebe stores is ongoing, or if it extends prior to mid-November 2014. </p>
<div id="attachment_28930" style="width: 610px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a class="lightbox" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/goodshophappywinter.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-28930" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/goodshophappywinter-600x356.png" alt="The card fraud shop &quot;goodshop[dot]bz&quot; is selling thousands of cards in its &quot;Happy Winter Update.&quot;" width="600" height="356" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">The card fraud shop &#8220;goodshop[dot]bz&#8221; is selling thousands of cards in its &#8220;Happy Winter Update.&#8221;</p></div>
<p><span id="more-28924"></span></p>
<p>There is no data to suggest that the apparent card breach at Bebe extends to the company&#8217;s online store. The items for sale at Goodshop are not cards, per se, but instead data copied from the magnetic stripe on the backs of credit cards. Armed with this information, thieves can re-encode the data onto new plastic and then use the counterfeit cards to buy high-priced items at big box stores, goods that can be quickly resold for cash (think iPads and gift cards, for example).</p>
<p>The most common way that thieves steal this type of card data is by hacking into cash registers at retail locations and planting malicious software that surreptitiously records mag stripe data when cards are swiped through the machines. The breaches at Home Depot, Target, Neiman Marcus, Michaels and other break-ins first detailed on this blog were all powered by malware that thieves planted on point-of-sale systems. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/banks-credit-card-breach-at-bebe-stores/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>41</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Be Wary of ‘Order Confirmation’ Emails</title>
		<link>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/be-wary-of-order-confirmation-emails/</link>
		<comments>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/be-wary-of-order-confirmation-emails/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 16:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BrianKrebs]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Latest Warnings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spam Nation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Coming Storm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[asprox botnet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[malcovery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trend micro]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=28907</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[If you receive an email this holiday season asking you to "confirm" an online e-commerce order or package shipment, please resist the urge to click the included link or attachment: Malware purveyors and spammers are blasting these missives by the millions each day in a bid to trick people into giving up control over their computers and identities.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you receive an email this holiday season asking you to &#8220;confirm&#8221; an online e-commerce order or package shipment, please resist the urge to click the included link or attachment: Malware purveyors and spammers are blasting these missives by the millions each day in a bid to trick people into giving up control over their computers and identities.</p>
<div id="attachment_28909" style="width: 610px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/hd-asprox.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-28909" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/hd-asprox-600x273.png" alt="An &quot;order confirmation&quot; malware email blasted out by the Asprox spam botnet recently. " width="600" height="273" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">An &#8220;order confirmation&#8221; malware email blasted out by the Asprox spam botnet recently.</p></div>
<p>Seasonal scams like these are a perennial scourge of the holidays, mainly because the methods they employ are reliably successful. Crooks understand that it&#8217;s easier to catch would-be victims off-guard during the holidays. This goes even for people who generally know better than to click on links and attachments in emails that spoof trusted brands and retailers, because this is a time of year when many people are intensely focused on making sure their online orders arrive before Dec. 25.</p>
<div id="attachment_28910" style="width: 610px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/wm-asprox.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-28910" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/wm-asprox-600x308.png" alt="This Asprox malware email poses as a notice about a wayward package from a WalMart  order." width="600" height="308" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">This Asprox malware email poses as a notice about a wayward package from a WalMart order.</p></div>
<p>According to <a title="http://www.malcovery.com" href="http://www.malcovery.com" target="_blank">Malcovery</a>, a company that closely tracks email-based malware attacks, these phony &#8220;order confirmation&#8221; spam campaigns began around Thanksgiving, and use both booby-trapped links and attached files in a bid to infect recipients&#8217; Windows PCs with the malware that powers the <strong>Asprox spam botnet</strong>.<span id="more-28907"></span></p>
<p>Asprox is a nasty Trojan that harvests email credentials and other passwords from infected machines, turns the host into a zombie for relaying junk email (such as the pharmaceutical spam detailed in <a title="http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/07/pre-order-your-copy-of-spam-nation-now/" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/07/pre-order-your-copy-of-spam-nation-now/" target="_blank">my new book Spam Nation</a>), and perpetuates additional Asprox malware attacks. Asprox also deploys a scanning module that forces hacked PCs to scan websites for vulnerabilities that can be used to hack the sites and foist malware on visitors to that site. For an exhaustive and fairly recent analysis of Asprox, see <a title="http://www.trendmicro.com/cloud-content/us/pdfs/security-intelligence/white-papers/wp-asprox-reborn.pdf" href="http://www.trendmicro.com/cloud-content/us/pdfs/security-intelligence/white-papers/wp-asprox-reborn.pdf" target="_blank">this writeup</a> (PDF) from <strong>Trend Micro</strong>.</p>
<div id="attachment_28911" style="width: 610px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/tg-asprox.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-28911" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/tg-asprox-600x373.png" alt="Target is among the many brands being spoofed by Asprox this holiday season." width="600" height="373" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Target is among the many brands being spoofed by Asprox this holiday season.</p></div>
<p>Malcovery notes that the Asprox spam emails use a variety of subject lines, including &#8220;Acknowledgment of Order,&#8221; &#8220;Order Confirmation,&#8221; &#8220;Order Status,&#8221; &#8220;Thank you for buying from [insert merchant name here]&#8221;, and a &#8220;Thank you for your order.&#8221;</p>
<p>If you receive an email from a recognized brand that references an issue with an online or in-store order and you think it might be legitimate, <em>do not click the embedded links or attachment</em>. Instead, open up a Web browser and visit the merchant site in question. Generally speaking, legitimate communications about order issues will reference an order number and/or some other data points specific to the transaction &#8212; information that can be used to look up the order status at the merchant&#8217;s Web site. I know I&#8217;m probably preaching to the choir for the loyal readers of this site, but I&#8217;m sure most of you have friends and relatives who could use a reminder about all of this. Please feel free to forward them a link to this story.</p>
<div id="attachment_28918" style="width: 610px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/cc-asprox.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-28918" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/cc-asprox-600x300.png" alt="Image: Malcovery" width="600" height="300" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Image: Malcovery</p></div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/be-wary-of-order-confirmation-emails/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>84</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sony Breach May Have Exposed Employee Healthcare, Salary Data</title>
		<link>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/sony-breach-may-have-exposed-employee-healthcare-salary-data/</link>
		<comments>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/sony-breach-may-have-exposed-employee-healthcare-salary-data/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 16:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BrianKrebs]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[A Little Sunshine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fbi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[packetninjas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Snort]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sony Pictures breach]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=28882</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The recent hacker break-in at Sony Pictures Entertainment appears to have involved the theft of far more than unreleased motion pictures: According to multiple sources, the intruders also stole more than 25 gigabytes of sensitive data on tens of thousands of Sony employees, including Social Security numbers, medical and salary information. What&#8217;s more, it&#8217;s beginning [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The recent hacker break-in at <strong>Sony Pictures Entertainment</strong> appears to have involved the theft of far more than unreleased motion pictures: According to multiple sources, the intruders also stole more than 25 gigabytes of sensitive data on tens of thousands of Sony employees, including Social Security numbers, medical and salary information. What&#8217;s more, it&#8217;s beginning to look like the attackers may have destroyed data on an unknown number of internal Sony systems. </p>
<div id="attachment_28884" style="width: 295px" class="wp-caption alignright"><a class="lightbox" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/pwc-sony.png"><img class="size-medium wp-image-28884" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/pwc-sony-285x185.png" alt="Screen shot from an internal audit report allegedly stolen from Sony." width="285" height="185" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Screen shot from an internal audit report allegedly stolen from Sony and circulating on file-trading networks.</p></div>
<p>Several files being traded on torrent networks seen by this author include a global Sony employee list, a Microsoft Excel file that includes the name, location, employee ID, network username, base salary and date of birth for more than 6,800 individuals.</p>
<p>Sony officials could not be immediately reached for comment; a press hotline for the company rang for several minutes without answer, and email requests to the company went unanswered.  But a comprehensive search on <strong>LinkedIn</strong> for dozens of the names in the list indicate virtually all correspond to current or former Sony employees.</p>
<p>Another file being traded online appears to be a status report from April 2014 listing the names, dates of birth, SSNs and health savings account data on more than 700 Sony employees. Yet another apparently purloined file&#8217;s name suggests it was the product of an internal audit from accounting firm <strong>Pricewaterhouse Coopers</strong>, and includes screen shots of dozens of employee federal tax records and other compensation data.</p>
<p>The latest revelations come more than a week after a cyberattack on Sony Pictures Entertainment brought down the company&#8217;s corporate email systems. A Sony spokesperson <a title="http://www.reuters.com/article/2014/12/02/us-sony-cybersecurity-malware-idUSKCN0JF3FE20141202" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2014/12/02/us-sony-cybersecurity-malware-idUSKCN0JF3FE20141202" target="_blank">told Reuters</a> that the company has since &#8220;restored a number of important services&#8221; and was &#8220;working closely with law enforcement officials to investigate the matter.&#8221;</p>
<div id="attachment_28892" style="width: 295px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><a class="lightbox" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/filesfromsony.png"><img class="size-medium wp-image-28892" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/filesfromsony-285x386.png" alt="Some of the files apparently taken from Sony that are now being traded on file-sharing networks." width="285" height="386" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Some of the files apparently taken from Sony that are now being traded on file-sharing networks.</p></div>
<p>Several media outlets reported at the time that Sony employees had been <a title="https://twitter.com/JamesDeanTimes/status/538253074876612608" href="https://twitter.com/JamesDeanTimes/status/538253074876612608" target="_blank">warned</a> not to connect to the company&#8217;s corporate network or to check email, and noted that Sony&#8217;s IT departments had instructed employees to turn off their computers as well as disable Wi-Fi on all mobile devices.&#8221; Other reports cited unnamed investigators pointing to North Korean hackers as the source of the attack, although those reports could not be independently confirmed.</p>
<p>Such extreme precautions would make sense if the company&#8217;s network was faced with a cyber threat designed to methodically destroy files on corporate computers. Indeed, the FBI this week released a restricted &#8220;Flash Alert&#8221; warning of just such a threat, about an unnamed attack group that has been using malware designed to wipe computer hard drives &#8212; and the underlying &#8220;<a title="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Master_boot_record" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Master_boot_record" target="_blank">master boot record</a>&#8221; (MBR) on the affected systems &#8212; of all data.</p>
<p>KrebsOnSecurity obtained a copy of the alert, which includes several file names and hashes (long strings of letters and numbers that uniquely identify files) corresponding to the file-wiping malware. The FBI does not specify where the malware was found or against whom it might have been used, noting only that &#8220;the FBI has high confidence that these indicators are being used by CNE [computer network exploitation] operators for further network exploitation.&#8221; The report also says the language pack referenced by the malicious files is Korean.</p>
<p><span id="more-28882"></span></p>
<p>The FBI alert references several network traffic &#8220;signatures&#8221; that organizations can use to detect the traffic seen in previous attacks from this malware &#8212; traffic that appears to beacon back to (most likely compromised) systems in Thailand, Poland and Italy. But the alert also says this type of vigilance may only serve to let organizations know that their files are currently in the process of being deleted.</p>
<p>&#8220;The following <a title="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Snort_%28software%29" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Snort_%28software%29" target="_blank">Snort</a> signature can be used to detect the beacon traffic, though by the time the beacons occur, the destructive process of wiping the files has begun,&#8221; the alert warned.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s the Snort signature, in case this is useful for any readers who didn&#8217;t get this memo:</p>
<p>Alert tcp any any &#8211; &gt; [88.53.215.64, 217.96.33.164, 203.131.222.102] [8080, 8000] (msg: “wiper_callout”;<br />
dsize:42;  content:  “|ff  ff  ff  ff|”;  offset:  26;  depth:  4;  sid:  314;</p>
<p><strong>Update: 1:58 p.m. ET:</strong> Multiple sources are reporting that the links to the torrents for the stolen Sony internal data were posted on Pastebin late Monday morning. Less than an hour after that post went live, the individual hosts that were sharing copies of the Sony data came under sustained denial-of-service attacks apparently aimed at keeping the files from being shared with other torrent users.</p>
<p>Also, the security guys over at Packetninjas have posted <a title="http://logfile.packetninjas.net/related-malware-to-sony-breach/" href="http://logfile.packetninjas.net/related-malware-to-sony-breach/" target="_blank">a useful write-up</a> on a malware sample they spotted from early July 2014 that matches the file name of the malware described in the FBI&#8217;s Flash alert about the file-wiping malware. Packetninjas notes that the file also was calling home to the same control server in Thailand that was documented in this week&#8217;s FBI alert.</p>
<p><a title="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/tree.txt" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/tree.txt" target="_blank">This file directory tree</a>, included in the leaked data, offers a glimpse into the sheer volume of files apparently compromised in this breach.</p>
<p>This is a developing story. More to come. Stay tuned.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/sony-breach-may-have-exposed-employee-healthcare-salary-data/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>74</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>KrebsOnSecurity on CBS’s ’60 Minutes’</title>
		<link>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/krebsonsecurity-on-cbss-60-minutes/</link>
		<comments>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/krebsonsecurity-on-cbss-60-minutes/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 17:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BrianKrebs]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Other]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[60 Minutes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bill Whitacker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Krebs on 60 Minuites]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=28872</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In case any of you loyal readers missed it, KrebsOnSecurity.com and its author were featured in a 60 Minutes interview last night on the credit and debit card breaches that have hit countless retailers and consumers over the past year. I spent more than a dozen hours with 60 Minutes producers, film crews and the [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In case any of you loyal readers missed it, <strong>KrebsOnSecurity.com</strong> and its author were featured in a<em> 60 Minutes</em> interview last night on the credit and debit card breaches that have hit countless retailers and consumers over the past year.</p>
<p><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/60mk.png"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-28873" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/60mk-600x343.png" alt="60mk" width="600" height="343" /></a></p>
<p>I spent more than a dozen hours with 60 Minutes producers, film crews and the host of this segment &#8212; CBS&#8217;s <a title="http://www.cbsnews.com/team/bill-whitaker/" href="http://www.cbsnews.com/team/bill-whitaker/" target="_blank">Bill Whitaker</a>, so I&#8217;m glad they were able to use as much footage as they did. Leading up to the filming, the producer of the show asked some very incisive questions &#8212; some of which I didn&#8217;t know the answers to myself &#8212; and I was hoping the segment would address some of the less discussed issues that contribute to this epidemic of card breaches. But, alas, I hope to explore some of those questions in future posts.</p>
<p>A link to a video and transcript of the program is <a title="http://www.cbsnews.com/news/swiping-your-credit-card-and-hacking-and-cybercrime/" href="http://www.cbsnews.com/news/swiping-your-credit-card-and-hacking-and-cybercrime/" target="_blank">here</a>.<span id="more-28872"></span></p>
<p>Much of the segment was shot in a nearby hotel. The rest of it was filmed right in my living room. The 60 Minutes crew had so much camera, sound and lighting gear set up in that room that they actually had to put a ton of other equipment in our kitchen (see the admittedly blurry picture below).</p>
<div id="attachment_28874" style="width: 610px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/60mcrew.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-28874" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/60mcrew-600x800.jpg" alt="Film crew working for CBS, in my kitchen." width="600" height="800" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Film crew working for CBS, in my kitchen.</p></div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/12/krebsonsecurity-on-cbss-60-minutes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>60</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Friday, Cyber Monday for Crooks, Too!</title>
		<link>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/black-friday-cyber-monday-for-crooks-too/</link>
		<comments>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/black-friday-cyber-monday-for-crooks-too/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 19:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BrianKrebs]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[A Little Sunshine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Fraud 2.0]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black Friday]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cyber Monday]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=28841</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Underground cybercrime shops that sell credit and debit card accounts stolen from retailers are slashing prices and promoting their own Black Friday and Cyber Monday sales as fraudsters gear up for the busy holiday shopping season.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Underground cybercrime shops that sell credit and debit card accounts stolen from retailers are slashing prices and promoting their own Black Friday and Cyber Monday sales as fraudsters gear up for the busy holiday shopping season.</p>
<p>Card data stolen from main street retailers, a.k.a. &#8220;dumps,&#8221; is sold to crooks who encode the numbers onto new plastic and go shopping for high-priced electronics and gift cards at big box stores. Other shops sell mainly stolen card numbers, expiration dates and card security codes that can only be used to shop at online retailers. </p>
<p>Have a look at the slide show below, which features multiple advertisements pushed out by some of the most bustling crime shops competing for buyers with discounts and promotions. You might have to scroll down a bit to see the slideshow. Advance the slides by hovering over the right edge of the image and clicking the arrow that appears.</p>
<p><iframe src='http://cdn.knightlab.com/libs/timeline/latest/embed/index.html?source=0Au2brCFyl25KdHh3YkNQbElOeWhza0RPdmllc3RlS2c&#038;font=Bevan-PotanoSans&#038;maptype=toner&#038;lang=en&#038;start_zoom_adjust=10&#038;height=900' width='100%' height='900' frameborder='0'></iframe></p>
<p>It&#8217;s nearly impossible for consumers to tell how secure a main street or online merchant is, so it&#8217;s best just to shop as if they&#8217;re all compromised. That is, if you have the choice between using a credit or debit card, shop with your credit card. <span id="more-28841"></span></p>
<p>Sure, the card associations and your bank will be quick to point out that you&#8217;re not liable for fraudulent charges that you report in a timely manner, but this assurance rings hollow for many who find their checking accounts emptied by card thieves after shopping at a breached merchant with a debit card. Who pays for the fees levied against you by different merchants when your checks bounce? You do. Does the bank reimburse you when your credit score takes a ding because your mortgage or car payment was late? Don&#8217;t hold your breath.</p>
<p>Also, if you&#8217;re shopping online this holiday season, be wary of phantom stores. If you don’t know much about the seller that has the item you want to buy, take a few minutes to investigate its online reputation. It’s not uncommon for bargain basement, phantom Web sites to materialize during the holiday season and vanish forever not long afterward. If you’re buying merchandise from an online store that is brand new, the risk that you will get scammed increases significantly. But how do you know the lifespan of a site selling that must-have gadget at the lowest price? One easy way to get a quick idea is to run <a href="http://whois.domaintools.com/krebsonsecurity.com" title="http://whois.domaintools.com/krebsonsecurity.com">a basic WHOIS search</a> on the site’s domain name. The more recent the site&#8217;s &#8220;creation date,&#8221; the more likely it is a phantom store.</p>
<p>Be careful what you agree to: Check to make sure you know how long the item will take to be shipped, and that you understand the store’s return policies. Also, keep an eye out for hidden surcharges, and be wary of blithely clicking “ok” during the checkout process. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/black-friday-cyber-monday-for-crooks-too/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>48</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Skimmer Innovation: ‘Wiretapping’ ATMs</title>
		<link>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/skimmer-innovation-wiretapping-atms/</link>
		<comments>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/skimmer-innovation-wiretapping-atms/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2014 19:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BrianKrebs]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All About Skimmers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ATM Skimmers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EAST]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eavesdropping skimmers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European ATM Security Team]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[insert skimmer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lachlan Gunn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wiretapping skimmers]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=28816</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Banks in Europe are warning about the emergence of a rare form of ATM skimmer involving a wire-like device that is inserted through a tiny hole cut in the cash machine's front. The hole is covered up by a fake decal, and the thieves somehow attach the device to the place inside the ATM where the customer's card is inserted.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Banks in Europe are warning about the emergence of a rare, virtually invisible form of ATM skimmer involving a so-called &#8220;wiretapping&#8221; device that is inserted through a tiny hole cut in the cash machine&#8217;s front. The hole is covered up by a fake decal, and the thieves then use custom-made equipment to attach the device to ATM&#8217;s internal card reader.</p>
<p>According to the <a title="https://www.european-atm-security.eu/" href="https://www.european-atm-security.eu/" target="_blank">European ATM Security Team</a> (EAST), a nonprofit that represents banks in 29 countries, financial institutions in two countries recently reported ATM attacks in which the card data was compromised internally by &#8220;wire-tapping&#8221; or &#8220;eavesdropping&#8221; on the customer transaction. The image below shows some criminal equipment used to perpetrate these eavesdropping attacks.</p>
<div id="attachment_28817" style="width: 610px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/wiretapping.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-28817" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/wiretapping-600x421.png" alt="Equipment used by crooks to conduct &quot;eavesdropping&quot; or &quot;wiretapping&quot; attacks on ATMs." width="600" height="421" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Equipment used by crooks to conduct &#8220;eavesdropping&#8221; or &#8220;wiretapping&#8221; attacks on ATMs. Source: EAST.</p></div>
<p>&#8220;The criminals cut a hole in the fascia around the card reader where the decal is situated,&#8221; EAST described in a recent, non-public report. &#8220;A device is then inserted and connected internally onto the card reader, and the hole covered with a fake decal&#8221;<br />
[pictured, bottom right].</p>
<p>Pictured above are what appear to be wires that are fed into the machine with some custom-made rods. It looks like the data is collected by removing the decal, fishing out the wire attached to the ATM&#8217;s card reader, and connecting it to a handheld data storage device.</p>
<p>I sought clarification from EAST about how the device works. Most skimmers are card slot overlay devices that work by using a built-in component which reads the account data off of the magnetic stripe when the customer inserts the card. But <strong>Lachlan Gunn</strong>, EAST&#8217;s executive director, suggested that this device intercepts the card data from the legitimate card reader on the inside of the ATM. He described the wiretapping device this way:</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s where a tap is attached to the pre-read head or read head of the card reader,&#8221; Lachlan said. &#8220;The card data is then read through the tap. We still classify it as skimming, but technically the magnetic stripe [on the customer/victim&#8217;s card] is not directly skimmed as the data is intercepted.&#8221;</p>
<p>The <a title="http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/08/stealthy-razor-thin-atm-insert-skimmers/" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/08/stealthy-razor-thin-atm-insert-skimmers/" target="_blank">last report in my ATM skimming series</a> showcased some major innovations in so-called &#8220;insert skimmers,&#8221; card-skimming devices made to fix snugly and invisibly inside the throat of the card acceptance slot. EAST&#8217;s new report includes another, slightly more advanced, insert skimmer that&#8217;s being called an &#8220;insert transmitter skimmer.&#8221;</p>
<p>Like the one pictured below, an insert transmitter skimmer is made up of two steel plates and an internal battery that lasts approximately one to two weeks. &#8220;They do not store data, but transmit it directly to a receiving device &#8212; probably placed less than 1 meter from the ATM.<span id="more-28816"></span></p>
<div id="attachment_28818" style="width: 610px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/insertskim11-14.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-28818" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/insertskim11-14-600x279.png" alt="An insert transmitter skimmer. Source: EAST." width="600" height="279" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">An insert transmitter skimmer. Source: EAST.</p></div>
<p>Both of these card skimming technologies rely on hidden cameras to steal customer PIN codes. In a typical skimming attack involving devices that lay directly on top of the card acceptance slot, the hidden camera is a pinhole spy cam that is embedded inside the card slot overlay and angled toward the PIN pad. Just as often, the camera is hidden in a false panel affixed directly above the PIN pan with the pinhole pointed downward.</p>
<p>According to east, the use of false sidebar panels is becoming more prevalent (see image below for an example). It is not unusual for hidden cameras to be <a title="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/01/lmpinhole.jpg" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/01/lmpinhole.jpg" target="_blank">obscured inside of phony brochure racks as well</a>.</p>
<p><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/sidepanels.png"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-28825" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/sidepanels.png" alt="sidepanels" width="551" height="750" /></a></p>
<p>As this and <a title="http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/07/the-rise-of-thin-mini-and-insert-skimmers/" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/07/the-rise-of-thin-mini-and-insert-skimmers/" target="_blank">other insert skimmer attacks</a> show, it’s getting tougher to spot ATM skimming devices. It’s best to focus instead on protecting your own physical security while at the cash machine. If you visit an ATM that looks strange, tampered with, or out of place, try to find another ATM. Use only machines in public, well-lit areas, and avoid ATMs in secluded spots.</p>
<p>Last, but certainly not least, cover the PIN pad with your hand when entering your PIN: That way, if even if the thieves somehow skim your card, there is less chance that they will be able to snag your PIN as well. You’d be amazed at <a title="http://krebsonsecurity.com/2012/09/a-handy-way-to-foil-atm-skimmer-scams/" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/2012/09/a-handy-way-to-foil-atm-skimmer-scams/" target="_blank">how many people fail to take this basic precaution</a>. Yes, there is still a chance that thieves could use a PIN-pad overlay device to capture your PIN, but in my experience these are far less common than hidden cameras (and quite a bit more costly for thieves who aren’t making their own skimmers).</p>
<p><center><iframe src="//www.youtube.com/embed/JbDdsUh_sTg" width="420" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></center>Are you as fascinated by ATM skimmers as I am? Check out my series on this topic, <a title="http://krebsonsecurity.com/all-about-skimmers/" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/all-about-skimmers/" target="_blank">All About Skimmers</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/skimmer-innovation-wiretapping-atms/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>49</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adobe Pushes Critical Flash Patch</title>
		<link>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/adobe-pushes-critical-flash-patch/</link>
		<comments>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/adobe-pushes-critical-flash-patch/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 18:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BrianKrebs]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Latest Warnings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time to Patch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adobe Flash Player update]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exploit kit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[f-secure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kafeine]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=28811</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[For the second time this month, Adobe has issued a security update for its Flash Player software. New versions are available for Windows, Mac and Linux versions of Flash. The patch provides additional protection on a vulnerability that Adobe fixed earlier this year for which attackers appear to have devised unique and active exploits.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For the second time this month, <strong>Adobe</strong> has issued a security update for its <strong>Flash Player</strong> software. New versions are available for <strong>Windows</strong>, <strong>Mac</strong> and <strong>Linux</strong> versions of Flash. The patch provides additional protection on a vulnerability that Adobe fixed earlier this year for which attackers appear to have devised unique and active exploits.</p>
<p><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/brokenflash-a.png"><img class="alignright  wp-image-18875" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/brokenflash-a.png" alt="brokenflash-a" width="190" height="162" /></a>Adobe recommends users of the Adobe Flash Player desktop runtime for Windows and Macintosh update to <em>v. 15.0.0.239</em> by visiting the Adobe Flash Player Download Center, or via the update mechanism within the product when prompted. Adobe Flash Player for Linux has been updated to <em>v. 11.2.202.424. </em></p>
<p>According to Adobe, these updates provide additional hardening against CVE-2014-8439, which was fixed in a Flash patch that the company released in <a title="http://helpx.adobe.com/security/products/flash-player/apsb14-22.html" href="http://helpx.adobe.com/security/products/flash-player/apsb14-22.html" target="_blank">October 2014</a>. The bulletin for this update is <a title="http://helpx.adobe.com/security/products/flash-player/apsb14-26.html" href="http://helpx.adobe.com/security/products/flash-player/apsb14-26.html" target="_blank">here</a>. Finnish security firm <strong>F-Secure</strong> <a title="https://www.f-secure.com/weblog/archives/00002768.html" href="https://www.f-secure.com/weblog/archives/00002768.html" target="_blank">says</a> it reported the flaw to Adobe after receiving information from independent researcher <a title="http://malware.dontneedcoffee.com/" href="http://malware.dontneedcoffee.com/" target="_blank">Kafeine</a> that indicated the vulnerability was being exploited in-the-wild by an exploit kit (malicious software designed to be stitched into hacked Web sites and foist malware on visitors via browser flaws like this one).<span id="more-28811"></span></p>
<p>To see which version of Flash you have installed, check <a title="https://www.adobe.com/software/flash/about/" href="https://www.adobe.com/software/flash/about/" target="_blank">this link</a>. IE10/IE11 on Windows 8.x and Chrome should auto-update their versions of Flash.</p>
<p>The most recent versions of Flash are available from the <a title="http://get.adobe.com/flashplayer/" href="http://get.adobe.com/flashplayer/" target="_blank">Flash home page</a>, but beware potentially unwanted add-ons, like McAfee Security Scan. To avoid this, uncheck the pre-checked box before downloading, or grab your OS-specific Flash download from <a title="http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/distribution3.html" href="http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/distribution3.html" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
<p>Windows users who browse the Web with anything other than Internet Explorer may need to apply this patch twice, once with IE and again using the alternative browser (Firefox, Opera, e.g.).</p>
<p><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/adobeflash11-14.png"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-28814" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/adobeflash11-14-600x189.png" alt="adobeflash11-14" width="600" height="189" /></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/adobe-pushes-critical-flash-patch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>37</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spam Nation Book Tour Highlights</title>
		<link>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/spam-nation-book-tour-highlights/</link>
		<comments>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/spam-nation-book-tour-highlights/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 20:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BrianKrebs]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Spam Nation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bloomberg News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBS 60 Minutes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charlie Rose]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fresh Air]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gayle King]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Herb Weisbaum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jim Bohannon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Norah O'Donnell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spam Nation book tour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terri Gross]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA Today]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://krebsonsecurity.com/?p=28774</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Greetings from sunny Austin, Texas, where I'm getting ready to wrap up a week-long book tour that began in New York City, then blazed through Chicago, San Francisco, and Seattle. I've been trying to tweet links to various media interviews about Spam Nation over the past week, but wanted to offer a more comprehensive account and to share some highlights of the tour]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Greetings from sunny Austin, Texas, where I&#8217;m getting ready to wrap up a week-long book tour that began in New York City, then blazed through Chicago, San Francisco, and Seattle. I&#8217;ve been trying to tweet links to various media interviews about<strong> <em>Spam Nation</em></strong> over the past week, but wanted to offer a more comprehensive account and to share some highlights of the tour.</p>
<p>For three days starting last Sunday, I was in New York City &#8212; doing a series of back-to-back television and radio interviews. Prior to leaving for New York, I taped television interviews with <strong>Jeffrey Brown</strong> at the <strong>PBS NewsHour</strong>; the <a title="http://www.pbs.org/newshour/bb/spam-nation-your-outdated-internet-browser-is-a-gateway-for-cyber-attacks/" href="http://www.pbs.org/newshour/bb/spam-nation-your-outdated-internet-browser-is-a-gateway-for-cyber-attacks/" target="_blank">first segment</a> delves into some of the points touched on in the book, and the <a title="http://www.pbs.org/newshour/rundown/think-can-go-grid-harder-realize/" href="http://www.pbs.org/newshour/rundown/think-can-go-grid-harder-realize/" target="_blank">second piece</a> is titled &#8220;Why it&#8217;s harder than you think to go &#8216;off the grid&#8217;.&#8221;</p>
<p><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/cbs-tm.png"><img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-28776" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/cbs-tm-600x306.png" alt="cbs-tm" width="600" height="306" /></a></p>
<p>On Monday, I was fortunate to once again be a guest on <strong>Terri Gross</strong>&#8216;s show <strong>Fresh Air</strong>, which you can hear at <a title="http://www.npr.org/blogs/alltechconsidered/2014/11/18/364730954/how-a-feud-between-two-russian-companies-fueled-a-spam-nation" href="http://www.npr.org/blogs/alltechconsidered/2014/11/18/364730954/how-a-feud-between-two-russian-companies-fueled-a-spam-nation" target="_blank">this link</a>. Tuesday morning began with a five-minute appearance on <strong>CBS This Morning</strong>, which included a sit-down with <strong>Charlie Rose</strong>, <strong>Gayle King</strong> and <strong>Norah O&#8217;Donnell</strong>. Later in the day, I was interviewed by the <a title="http://www.marketplace.org/shows/marketplace-tech/marketplace-tech-wednesday-november-19-2014" href="http://www.marketplace.org/shows/marketplace-tech/marketplace-tech-wednesday-november-19-2014" target="_blank">MarketPlace Tech Report</a>, <strong>MSNBC&#8217;s </strong><a title="http://www.msnbc.com/the-cycle/watch/use-these-tools-to-stop-cyber-criminals-360420931970" href="http://www.msnbc.com/the-cycle/watch/use-these-tools-to-stop-cyber-criminals-360420931970" target="_blank">The Cycle</a>, as well as the <strong>Tavis Smiley</strong> show. Wednesday was a mercifully light day, with just two interviews: <strong>KGO-AM</strong> and the <strong>Jim Bohannon Radio Show</strong>.<span id="more-28774"></span></p>
<p>Thursday&#8217;s round of media appearances began at around sunrise in the single-digit temperature Chicago suburbs. My driver from the hotel to all of these events took me aback at first. <strong>Roxanna</strong> was a petite blonde from Romania who could have just as easily been a supermodel. I thought for a moment someone was playing a practical joke when I first heard her &#8220;Gud mornink Meester Krebs&#8221; in a Eastern European accent upon stepping into <a title="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/rox.jpg" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/rox.jpg" target="_blank">her Town Car</a>, but Roxanna was a knowledgeable driver who got us everywhere on time and didn&#8217;t take any crap from anyone on the road.</p>
<p><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/wcl-ji.png"><img class="alignright  wp-image-28785" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/wcl-ji-285x362.png" alt="wcl-ji" width="219" height="278" /></a> The first of those interviews was a television segment for <a title="http://wgntv.com/2014/11/20/how-to-protect-yourself-against-spam-emails/" href="http://wgntv.com/2014/11/20/how-to-protect-yourself-against-spam-emails/" target="_blank">WGN News</a> and a taped interview with <strong>TouchVision</strong>, followed by my first interview <a title="http://windycitylive.com/episodes/Brian-Krebs--cybersecurity-expert/9544217" href="http://windycitylive.com/episodes/Brian-Krebs--cybersecurity-expert/9544217" target="_blank">in front of a studio audience at Windy City Live</a>.  The guest who went on right before me was none other than the motivational speaker/life coach <a title="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tony_Robbins" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tony_Robbins" target="_blank">Tony Robbins</a>, who is a tough act to follow and was also on the show to promote his new book. At six feet seven inches, Robbins is a larger-than-life guy whose mere presence almost took up half the green room. Anyway Mr. Robbins had quite the security detail, so I took <a title="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/stealthie.png" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/stealthie.png" target="_blank">this stealthie</a> of Tony as he was confined to the makeup chair prior to his appearance.</p>
<p>On Thursday afternoon, after an <a title="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/cheeburger.jpg" href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/cheeburger.jpg" target="_blank">obligatory lunch</a> at the infamous Billy Goat burger joint (the inspiration for the &#8220;<a title="https://screen.yahoo.com/gilda-radner-snl-skits/olympia-restaurant-000000640.html" href="https://screen.yahoo.com/gilda-radner-snl-skits/olympia-restaurant-000000640.html" target="_blank">Cheezborger, cheezborger, cheezborger</a>&#8221; Saturday Night Live skit) I visited the Sourcebooks office in Naperville, met many of the folks who worked on Spam Nation, signed a metric ton of books and<a title="https://twitter.com/toddstocke/status/535820729749889024/photo/1" href="https://twitter.com/toddstocke/status/535820729749889024/photo/1" target="_blank"> the company&#8217;s author wall</a>.</p>
<div id="attachment_28792" style="width: 295px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/naperville-e1416857473969.jpg"><img class="size-medium wp-image-28792" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/naperville-e1416857473969-285x213.jpg" alt="The Spam Nation signing in Naperville, IL." width="285" height="213" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">The Spam Nation signing in Naperville, IL.</p></div>
<p>After an amazing dinner with my sister and the CEO of Sourcebooks, we headed to my first book signing event just down the street. It was a well-attended event with some passionate readers and fans, including quite a few folks from <a title="https://twitter.com/burbsecwest" href="https://twitter.com/burbsecwest" target="_blank">@BurbsecWest</a> with whom I had beers afterwards.</p>
<p>On Friday, I hopped a plane to San Francisco and sat down for taped interviews with <strong>USA Today</strong> and <strong>Bloomberg News</strong>. The book signing that night at <a title="http://www.booksinc.net/book/9781402295614" href="http://www.booksinc.net/book/9781402295614" target="_blank">Books Inc.</a> drew a nice crowd and also was followed by some after-event celebration.</p>
<p>Departed for Seattle the next morning, and sat down for a studio interview with longtime newsman (and general mensch) <strong>Herb Weisbaum</strong> at <strong>KOMO-AM</strong>. The signing in Seattle, at <a title="http://www.thirdplacebooks.com/book/%5Bmodel%5D-243" href="http://www.thirdplacebooks.com/book/%5Bmodel%5D-243" target="_blank">Third Place Books</a>, was the largest turnout of all, and included a very inquisitive crowd that bought up all of the copies of Spam Nation that the store had on hand.</p>
<div id="attachment_28798" style="width: 610px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/seattlesigning-a-e1416858309241.jpg"><img class="size-large wp-image-28798" src="http://krebsonsecurity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/seattlesigning-a-e1416858309241-600x337.jpg" alt="Yours Truly at a book signing in Seattle's Third Place Books." width="600" height="337" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Book signing at Seattle&#8217;s Third Place Books.</p></div>
<p>If you&#8217;re planning to be in Austin tonight &#8212; Nov. 24 &#8212; consider stopping by <strong>B&amp;N Arboretum</strong> at 7:00 p.m. and get your copy of Spam Nation signed. I&#8217;ll be holding one more signing &#8212; 7:00 p.m. in Washington, D.C.&#8217;s <a title="http://www.politics-prose.com/event/book/brian-krebs-spam-nation-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-global-epidemic-to-your-fron" href="http://www.politics-prose.com/event/book/brian-krebs-spam-nation-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-global-epidemic-to-your-fron" target="_blank">Politics &amp; Prose</a> on Dec. 4.</p>
<p>For those on the fence about buying Spam Nation, <a title="http://www.slate.com/articles/technology/future_tense/2014/11/spam_nation_meet_the_russian_cybercrooks_behind_the_digital_threats_in_your.html" href="http://www.slate.com/articles/technology/future_tense/2014/11/spam_nation_meet_the_russian_cybercrooks_behind_the_digital_threats_in_your.html" target="_blank">Slate</a> and <a title="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/article/20141122122943-2460067-why-spammy-online-pharmacies-actually-have-amazing-customer-service?trk=object-title" href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/article/20141122122943-2460067-why-spammy-online-pharmacies-actually-have-amazing-customer-service?trk=object-title" target="_blank">LinkedIn</a> both ran excerpts of the book. Other reviews and interviews are available at <a title="http://fortune.com/2014/11/21/brian-krebs-spam-nation-organized-cybercrime/?utm_content=buffer1d6d9&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=facebook.com&amp;utm_campaign=buffer" href="http://fortune.com/2014/11/21/brian-krebs-spam-nation-organized-cybercrime/?utm_content=buffer1d6d9&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=facebook.com&amp;utm_campaign=buffer" target="_blank">Fortune.com</a>, <a title="http://news.yahoo.com/spam-nation-cybercrime-spam-far-224128994.html" href="http://news.yahoo.com/spam-nation-cybercrime-spam-far-224128994.html" target="_blank">Yahoo News</a>, and <a title="http://www.creditcards.com/credit-card-news/spam-nation-brian-krebs-data-black-market-1278.php" href="http://www.creditcards.com/credit-card-news/spam-nation-brian-krebs-data-black-market-1278.php" target="_blank">CreditCards.com</a>. Also, I was interviewed at length several times over the past month by <strong>CBS&#8217;s 60 Minutes</strong>, which is doing a segment on retail data breaches. That interview could air as early as Nov. 30. On that note, the <em>Minneapolis Star Tribune</em> ran <a title="http://www.startribune.com/local/283597021.html?page=1&amp;c=y" href="http://www.startribune.com/local/283597021.html?page=1&amp;c=y" target="_blank">a lengthy story</a> on Sunday that followed up on some information I first reported a year ago about a Ukrainian man thought to be tied to the Target breach, among others.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://krebsonsecurity.com/2014/11/spam-nation-book-tour-highlights/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>27</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
<!-- Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: http://www.w3-edge.com/wordpress-plugins/

Page Caching using memcached
Database Caching using memcached
Object Caching 696/697 objects using memcached

 Served from: krebsonsecurity.com @ 2014-12-05 23:32:38 by W3 Total Cache -->
